https://sdsc.org.sg/sdsc-privacy-policy/

Learn-to-Play Programme
Learn to Shoot (VI Shooting)
Career with Partner Organisations
Athlete Competition Partner (Boccia)
High Performance Para Athletics Coach (Long Jump)
Your privacy is important to us. The purpose of this
Privacy Policy is to inform you of how Singapore Disability Sports Council
(SDSC) manages personal data in accordance with the Personal Data Protection
Act 2012 (“the Act”). Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy so that
you know and understand the purposes for which we collect, use and disclose your
Personal Data.
By interacting with us, submitting information to us or
signing up for any promotions or services offered by us, you agree and consent
to Singapore Disability Sports Council, its related corporations and
affiliates, (collectively referred to herein as “SDSC”, “us”,
“we” or “our”), as well as our respective representatives
collecting, using, disclosing and sharing amongst themselves your Personal
Data, and disclosing such Personal Data to SDSC’s authorised service providers
and relevant third parties in the manner set forth in this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy supplements but does not supersede nor replace any other consents you may have previously provided to SDSC nor does it affect any rights which SDSC may have at law in connection with the collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Data. SDSC may from time to time update this Privacy Policy to ensure that this Privacy Policy is consistent with our future developments, industry trends and/or any changes in legal or regulatory requirements. Subject to your rights at law, you agree to be bound by the prevailing terms of the Privacy Policy as updated from time to time on our websites. Please check regularly for updated information on the handling of your Personal Data.
1. Your Personal Data 1.1
In this Privacy Policy, “Personal Data” refers to any data or information about you from which you can be identified either (a) from that data; or (b) from that data and other information to which we have or are likely to have access. Examples of such Personal Data which you may provide to us include (depending on the nature of your interaction with us:(a) your name, NRIC, passport or other identification number, telephone number(s), mailing address, email address and any other information relating to you which you have provided us in any forms you may have submitted to us, or in other forms of interaction with you;(b) information about your use of SDSC’s website and services, including cookies, IP address, subscription account details and membership details, but only to the extent that SDSC may identify you from such information;(c) your employment history, education background, and income levels;(d) your payment related information, such as your bank account or credit card information, and your credit history; and(e) information about your usage of and interaction with our website and/or services including computer and connection information, device capability, bandwidth, statistics on page views, and traffic to and from our website.
2. Collection of Personal Data2.1
Generally, SDSC collects your Personal Data in the following ways: (a) when you submit forms relating to any of our products or services; (b) when you register for or use any of our services on websites owned or operated by us or when you register as a member of websites owned and/or operated by us, or use services on such websites;
(c) when you interact with our officers; (d) when you use some of our services; (e) when you establish any online accounts with us; (f) when you request that we contact you; (g) when you are contacted by, and respond to, our representatives and agents; (h) when you respond to our request for additional Personal Data (i) when you ask to be included in an email or other mailing list; (j) when you respond to our promotions and other initiatives; (k) when you submit a job application; (l) when you enter into tenancy agreements with us; (m) when we receive references from business partners and third parties, for example, where you have been referred by them; (n) when you submit your Personal Data to us for any other reason.
2.2 When you browse our website, you generally do so anonymously.2.3 If you provide us with any Personal Data relating to a third party (e.g. information of spouse, children, parents, employees and/or authorised representatives), by submitting such information to us, you represent to us that you have obtained the consent of the third party to you providing us with their Personal Data for the respective purposes.2.4
You should ensure that all Personal Data submitted to us is complete, accurate, true and correct. Failure on your part to do so may result in our inability to provide you with products and services you have requested.3 Purposes for the Collection, Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Data3.1 Generally, SDSC collects, uses and discloses your Personal Data for the following purposes: (a) responding to your queries and requests and responding to complaints; (b) managing the infrastructure and business operations of SDSC and complying with internal policies and procedures; (c) facilitating business asset transactions which may extend to any merger, acquisition or asset sale; (d) matching any Personal Data held which relates to you for any of the purposes listed herein; (e) verifying your identity; (f) preventing, detecting and investigating crime, including fraud and money-laundering, and analysing and managing other commercial risks; (g) protecting and enforcing our contractual and legal rights and obligations; (h) conducting audits, reviews and analysis of our internal processes, action planning and managing commercial risks; (i) preventing, detecting and investigating crime and managing the safety and security of our premises and services including but not limited to carrying out CCTV surveillance and conducting security clearances (j) compliance with any applicable rules, laws and regulations, codes of practice or guidelines or to assist in law enforcement and investigations by relevant authorities; and/or (k) any other purpose relating to any of the above.
3.2 In addition, SDSC may collect, use and disclose your Personal Data for the following purposes, depending on the nature of our relationship with you: (a) If you are a para athlete, official or technical official, or volunteer with us: (i) to process your application and signing an agreement with us; (ii) to maintain your record with us; (iii) to verify and process your personal particulars and payments in relation to provision of services to you; (iv) communicating with you to inform you of changes and development to SDSC policies, terms and conditions and other administrative information, including for the purposes of servicing you in relation to products and services offered to you; (v) resolving complaints and handling requests and enquiries; (vi) conducting market research for statistical, profiling and statistical analysis for the improvement of services provided to you; and (vii) the processing of your Personal Data in relation to any of the purposes stated above.
(b) If you use download or use any of SDSC’s Apps:
(i) to maintain your account with us and to ensure your access to the App; (ii) to verify and process your personal particulars and payments in relation to provision of goods and services connected to the App;(iii) to provide you with the goods and services which you have signed up for and to push news and events to you which may be relevant to you;(iv) communicating with you to inform you of changes and development to SDSC policies, terms and conditions and other administrative information, including for the purposes of servicing you in relation to products and services offered to you;(v) resolving complaints and handling requests and enquiries;(vi) conducting market research for statistical, profiling and statistical analysis for the improvement of services provided to you; and(vii) the processing of your Personal Data in relation to any of the purposes stated above.
(c) If you are a donor or sponsor of SDSC: (i) to verify and process your personal particulars and donations or sponsorships made to SDSC; (ii) communicating with you to inform you of changes and development to SDSC policies, terms and conditions and other administrative information, including for the purposes of servicing you in relation to products and services offered to you; (iii) resolving complaints and handling requests and enquiries;
3.3 In addition, where permitted under the Act, SDSC may also collect, use and disclose your Personal Data for the following purposes (which we may describe in our documents and agreements as “Additional Purposes” for the handling of Personal Data): (a) providing services, products and benefits to you, including promotions, loyalty and reward programmes; (b) matching Personal Data with other data collected for other purposes and from other sources (including third parties) in connection with the provision or offering of products and services, whether by SDSC or other third parties; (c) administering contests, competitions and conducting lucky draws, including, where necessary, in order to announce the results of these contests, competitions and lucky draws and identify and contact the winners, and in order to publicise and conduct marketing strictly related to these contests, competitions and lucky draws; (d) sending you details of products, services, special offers and rewards, either to our community generally, or of particular products and services which may be of interest to you; and (e) conducting market research, understanding and determining customer location, preferences and demographics for us to review, develop and improve our products, services and also develop special offers and marketing programmes.
3.4 If you have provided your Singapore telephone number(s) and have indicated that you consent to receiving marketing or promotional information via your Singapore telephone number(s), then from time to time, SDSC may contact you using such Singapore telephone number(s) (including via voice calls, sms, fax or other means) with information about our products and services (including discounts and special offers).3.5 In relation to particular products or services or in your interactions with us, we may also have specifically notified you of other purposes for which we collect, use or disclose your Personal Data. If so, then we will collect, use and disclose your Personal Data for these additional purposes as well, unless we have
specifically notified you otherwise. 4
Disclosure of Personal Data4.1 SDSC will take reasonable steps to protect your Personal Data against unauthorised disclosure. Subject to the provisions of any applicable law, this Personal Data may be disclosed, for the purposes listed above (where applicable), to the following third parties, whether they are located overseas or in Singapore: (a) SDSC affiliates; (b) agents, contractors or third party service providers who provide operational services to SDSC, such as telecommunications, information technology, payment, payroll, processing, training, market research, delivery services, storage, archival or other services to SDSC; (c) vendors or any third party business partners who offer goods and services or sponsor contests or other promotional programs on SDSC’s sites, whether in conjunction with us or not; (d) external business and charity partners in relation to corporate promotional events; (e) any business partner, investor, assignee or transferee (actual or prospective) to facilitate business asset transactions (which may extend to any merger, acquisition or asset sale; (f) anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer our rights and duties; (g) banks, credit card companies and their respective service providers; (h) our professional advisors such as our auditors and lawyers; (i) relevant government regulators or authority or law enforcement agency to comply with any laws or rules and regulations imposed by any governmental authority; and (j) any other party to whom you authorise us to disclose your personal data
5
Third-Party Sites5.1 Our website may contain links to other websites operated by third parties, such as our business partners. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of websites operated by third parties that are linked to our website. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of such third party websites. Some of these third party websites may be co-branded with our logo or trademark, even though they are not operated or maintained by us. Once you have left our website, you should check the applicable terms, conditions and policies of the third party website to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you. 6 Withdrawal, Access and Correction of your Personal Data6.1 Should you wish to withdraw consent to use of your Personal Data or obtain access to or make corrections to your Personal Data records, please log in to the relevant account through which the Personal Data was provided, if any, failing which please contact the relevant Personal Data Protection Officer, contact details of which are found in the Personal Data Protection Statement or similar document elsewhere on the relevant SDSC website.6.2 Please note that if your Personal Data has been provided to us by a third party, you should contact such party directly to make any queries, feedback, and access and correction requests to SDSC on your behalf.6.3 Please note that if you withdraw your consent to any or all use of your Personal Data, depending on the nature of your request, SDSC may not be in a position to continue to provide its products or services to you or administer any contractual relationship in place, and this may also result in the termination of any agreements with SDSC and your being in breach of your contractual obligations or undertakings, and SDSC’s legal rights and remedies in such event are expressly reserved.7 Governing Law7.1 This Privacy Policy shall be governed in all respects by the laws of Singapore.
© Singapore Disability Sports Council | 2020
